Podell, Bertram L.; Papers apap270
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General Subject Files, 1945-1968; Undated; 1; 6.0 cubic ft.
  - Standing Committees, 1965 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - State Platform, 1967 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Statistical Spreadsheets and Addresses, 1964; Undated (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Steingut Program, 1965 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Stenographic Services, 1965 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Summary of Bills, Undated (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Summer Jobs, 1965; Undated (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Surety Bonds Press Releases, 1966 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Tax Program, 1961-1962; 1964-1966 (Box 5 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Taxation (New York City), 1966 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Taxation (New York State), 1966 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Teacher Pensions (Correspondence), 1966; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Teacher Retirement Bill, 1966-1967 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Telegrams Sent, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Television-Radio-Etc., 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Terminal Leave Pay Municipal Employees, 1967 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Textbook Bill, 1966; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Transit, 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Transit, 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Transit Authority and Transit Workers Union, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Transit Fare Increase Press Releases, 1966 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Transportation, 1962; 1965; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Transportation, 1965; 1967 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Travia, Anthony J. (Speaker), 1965-1966; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, 1964-1966; Undated (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Twin Double, 1966 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Unanswered Correspondence (Insufficient Address), 1965 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Unanswered Letters (Out of District), 1965 (Box 6 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Vacationlands, 1964-1965 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Vassar College, 1967 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Voting Age (Correspondence), 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Voting Age (Press Releases), 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Voting Bill-18 Years Old, 1967 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Wagner, Robert (Mayor), 1965 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Water Commission, 1967 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Water Districts Press Releases (NYS), 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Water Metering Press Releases, 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Water Rates Press Releases, 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Water Resources Planning, 1965-1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Water Resources Planning Press Releases, 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Water Resources Statements, 1966; Undated (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Water Restrictions Press Releases, 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Water Supply Board Intro 6630 Correspondence, 1966 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Weapons Legislation, 1967 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Weintraub, 1965 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - World's Fair, 1965 (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Youman's, Mark R., 1966; Undated (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Young Democrats (New York State College), Undated (Box 7 (1-General Subject Files), Folder 20)
- Congressional Subject Files, 1963-1970; Undated; 2; 3.0 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains material related to Bertram Podell's tenure in the U.S. House of Representatives. In addition to bills, files contain news clippings and correspondence. A large majority of the files in this series are related to the Naval Applied Science Laboratory located in the Brooklyn Navy Yard.
  - Ad Hoc Committee Case Study Prepared for the Secretary of the Navy, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Administration: Additional Copies of Kennedy Tribute, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Agriculture: Elderly Exchange Food Stamps for Prepared Meals, 1969; Undated (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Agriculture: Food Stamp Reform Act of 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Agriculture: Human Nutrition Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Agriculture: National Pesticide Commission Act of 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Agriculture: Removal of Flaws in Food Stamp Program, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Agriculture: Terminate Sugar Quota for South Africa, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Agriculture Workers: National Labor Relations Act, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Aid to Polish Jewry, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Alternative Plan for the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - An Urban Problem of New York: A Test Case, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Appropriations: Supplemental Appropriations for Bilingual Education Act, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Appropriations: Supplemental Appropriations for Head Start for Fiscal 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Armed Forces: Congressional Medal of Honor to Apollo 8, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Armed Forces: Definition of Conscientious Objector, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Armed Forces: Health Care Benefits, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Armed Forces: Supreme Sacrifice Medal, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Armed Forces: To Create an Office of Defense Review, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Atomic Energy: Enrico Fermi Nuclear Accelerator, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Aviation: Airport and Airways Development Act of 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Aviation: CAB Authority in Relieving Airport Congestion, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Aviation: Civil Aircraft, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Aviation: Rate Reductions, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Aviation: Requirements for Air Traffic Controllers, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Banking: Crime Protection Insurance, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Broker Insurance Corporation, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Case for Retention of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Census Question Limitation, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights: Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Civil Service: Postal Pay Raise, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Commerce: FTC Investigation in Home Improvement Industry, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Commission: Afro-American History and Culture, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Commission: Astronauts Memorial in Cape Kennedy, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Commission: Chemicals in Peace and War, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Commission: Government Reorganization, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Commission: Temporary State Commission on Water Resources Planning, 1965 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Commission: To Establish a National Security Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Committee: Joint Committee to Investigate Crime, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Communications: Candidate Television Broadcast Time, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Congressional Committee: National Priorities and Resource Allocation, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Congressional Record, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Conservation: Bill of Rights, 1968-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Conservation: Marine Resources and Development Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Conservation: Mid-Atlantic States Air Pollution Control Compact, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Conservation: Susquehanna River Basin Compact, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Consumer: Department of Consumer Affairs, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Consumer: Intergovernmental Consumer Assistance and Protection Act, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Consumer: Protect Children From Toys or Other Articles, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Control Over Gun and Weapon Sales, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Crime: Assistance with the Rehabilitation of Criminal and Youth Offenders, 1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Crime: Criminal Activity in the 13th Congressional District, 1968 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Crime: Establishment of 7 Regional Law Enforcement Academies, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Draft Reform: Random Selection for Induction into the Armed Services, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Drug Abuse Traffic: Transportation of Drugs, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Drugs: Federal Drug Compendium, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Drugs: Generic Name of Drug on Drug Labels, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Drugs: To Establish a Commission on Marijuana, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Economic Analysis of the Transfer of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Education: Programs in Fiscal Year 1970, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Education: Aid to Children of Civilian Employees Killed Abroad, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Education: Grants for Drug Education Programs, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Education: Institutional Grants for Science Education, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Education: Loans to Citizens Studying in Foreign Schools, 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Education: Medical Education Bill of Rights of 1969 (Box 1 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Education: National Center on Educational Media and Materials for Handicapped, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Education: Services in Child Day Care Centers, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Education: Student Loan Program, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Election: TV Debate and Presidential Nominee Selection Act of 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Environment: Amending the Rules of the House to Provide For changes in the Committee on Environment, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Environment: Council on Environmental Quality, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Environment: Daily Determination of Environmental Pollution, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Environment: Environmental Quality Index, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Federal Assistance: Catalog, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Federal Property: Acquisition for Private Development, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Federal Reorganization: Legislative Reorganization Act of 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Federal Reorganization: Legislative Reorganization Act of 1969 (Compromise) (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Food: Food Stamp Act, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Foreign Affairs: Atlantic Union Resolution, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs: Hijacking of TWA Jet to Syria by Arab Guerillas, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs: Immediate Cease-Fire in Biafra, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Foreign Affairs: Nigerian-Biafran Relief, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Citizens Reunited, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Testing of MIRVs, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Treatment of American POWs in Vietnam, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs: U.S. Aid for Iraqi Jews, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Foundation: National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities of 1965, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Government Operations: GAO Disclosure, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Health: Grants for Disease Control, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Health: Grants for Training in Family Medicine, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Health: Hospital Modernization and Improvement Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Health: Labeling of Cigarette Packages, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Health: National Center for Population and Family Planning, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Health: National Kidney Disease Act of 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Health: National Lung Institute, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Health: Study of Malnutrition, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Health Insurance: National Catastrophic Illness Insurance Program, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Housing: Building Sciences Act of 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Housing: Low and Moderate Income Housing Provisions, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Housing: Supplemental Appropriations for Low and Moderate Income Housing, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Housing: Transfer Airspace for Housing, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Insurance: Federal Insurance Guaranty Corp., 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Interstate Commerce: Motion Pictures and TV Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Investigation on Chemical and biological Warfare, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Judiciary: Bingo Bill, 1967-1969; Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Judiciary: Citizenship for SP/4 Aaron Tawil, 1967-1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Judiciary: Newspaper Preservation Act, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Judiciary: Prohibit Investigations by Private Organizations of Congressional Employees, 1969; Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Judiciary: Public Disclosure by Public Officials, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Labor: Employment Opportunity, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Labor: Job Corps Shutdown, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Labor: Occupational Manpower Bill, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Labor: Pension and Employee Benefit Act of 1969, Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Lottery: Decline in Lottery Ticket Sales, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Maritime: Department of Maritime Affairs, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Maritime: Independent Federal Maritime Administration, 1967; 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Martin Luther King Jr., 1968 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Merchant Marine: Encourage Shipbuilding, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Merchant Marine: U.S. Cargo-Preference Laws, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - NASA: Research and Development, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Cooperative Work-Study Program, Undated (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: February Correspondence, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: April Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: May Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 60-61)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: June Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 62-63)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: July Correspondence, 1969 (Box 2 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 64-65)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: August Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: September Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: October Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory Inter-Office Memo, Undated (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Opportunities for Research, 1969; Undated (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Professional Papers and Patents, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Naval Applied Science Laboratory: Youth Opportunity Campaign, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Opportunity: Full Opportunity Act, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Opportunity: Full Opportunity Act, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Passports: Efficient and Convenient Passport Services, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Peace: Department of Peace, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Peace: Department of Peace, 1968-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Pollution: Clean Air Act, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Pollution: Comprehensive Water Quality Improvement Act of 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Works: Metro Areas of Redevelopment and Authorization, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Railroads: Method of Computing Interest, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Resources: Engineers to Work on Water Pollution, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Resources: National Water Pollution Disaster Fund, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Revenue: Tax Sharing Act of 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Rules: To Reform the Teller Vote Provision of the Committee of the Whole, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Safety: Section 5 of the Department of Transportation Act, 1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Science: National Science Foundation, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Selective Service: Prohibit Draftees in Undeclared Wars, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Selective Service: Selective Service Boards, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Selective Service: Selective Service Reform, 1967-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Social Science: National Commission on Libraries and Information, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Social Security: Disability Prior to 1967, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Social Security: Increased Benefits and Insurance for the Disabled, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Social Security: Monthly Benefits and Cost of Living, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Social Security: National Welfare Standards, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Social Security: Revision of Welfare System, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Social Security: Widow with Minor Children, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Summary and Analysis: The Case for Retention of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Summary of Presentation: The Case for Retention of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Tax Reform: Limit Farming Tax Deductions, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Tax Reform: Prohibit Percentage Depletion for Mines, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Tax Reform: Tax Reform Act of 1969, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Taxation: Deductible Moving Expenses, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Taxation: Double Personal Income Tax Exemption, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Taxation: Higher Education Funding Act of 1968, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Taxation: Withholding Earnings From Federal Employees, 1969 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Transportation, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Transportation, 1963-1965 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Transportation: Standards for Railroad Passenger Service, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Treaty on Chemical Warfare, 1968 (Box 3 (2-Congressional Subject Files), Folder 45)
- Bills and Resolutions, 1963-1967; Undated; 3; 1.2 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by legislation type and then chronologically by bill number.